defense-update.com 2011-01-05

# New Page

## Defense Update - Privacy Policy

Defense Update totally object to spam and will not take part in such process in any way. We won't use your email address for any other purpose than the one for which you originally gave it to us: to inform you about Defense Updates. This may include contacting subscribers to update information once in a while, and, from time to time, inviting some readers to participate in a readership survey.

##### Double opt-in and opt-out

We use confirmed opt-in (a.k.a. double opt-in), to ensure that only legitimate owners of an e-mail account are served. We offer an automated unsubscribe service. This service also provide subscribers with a change of address option.

##### Your name and e-mail address

We do not rent, swap or sell our lists with advertisers, other web sites or list brokers. We may engage in co-registration deals with other publishers, provided these partnerships are based on opt-in (i.e. you won't get anything from our partners unless you actively choose to get it). We consider our lists a business asset and we reserve the right to sell them if someone was to acquire our services. Such potential acquirer would have to commit to respecting this privacy policy and change it only with your active consent. 

If you post a comment on Defense-Update, we will use your e-mail to respond to you only. We don't collect or aggregate respondent's email for any purpose. 

##### Logging, Cookies, Web beacons and Third Party Advertising

We use third-party web-site statistics monitoring and advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/).

Among other 3rd party ad-serving systems operating on defense-Update, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Defense-Update site. Google's use of the [DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Security

We have put security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Only authorized personnel are allowed physical and/or digital access to servers and data. All servers and data backups are kept secure from physical and electronic intrusion by use of firewalls and redundant security systems, which are periodically evaluated and upgraded.

##### Legal Disclaimer

Personally Identifiable Information provided to Defense Update is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. We make every effort possible to preserve user privacy and anonymity; however, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein such action is necessary to comply with judicial proceedings, court orders or legal processes served on our Website. 

Defense Update, 2009
